Distortion, ripping through the fog and mist, downtown s
irens where the rebels exist, rips
cut corners like they're burning the ground, fast lanes
bleeding with the punk rock sound,
speed sign flickers but I don't slow down, don't slow down,
stereo blaring as I fly through
town, fly through town, sand friend concrete shakes under
tread, not gonna stop for a camera's
wed, flash on the avenue taking modern wheels, caught in
the web of the automated seal, big
bunters laughing as he flips a reel, speeding in the city
pays another meal, light slash
red as I go, can't stop now, won't slow, oh, pedal to the
metal but the street's all eyes,
silent snitches snapping from the lamplight skies, twenty
bucks gone in a traffic disguise,
every buck another Orwell surprise, tick it in the inbox it
's a bad routine, punk rock
downshot on the screen, flash on the avenue taking modern
wheels, caught in the web of
the automated seal, big bunters laughing as he flips a reel
, speeding in the city pays
another meal, light slash red as I go, can't stop now, won
't slow, uh-uh.